undergroundhiphop.com 2018-12-28

# UndergroundHipHop.com, LLC Privacy Policy | UGHH

Your privacy is important to us.  This Privacy Policy is applicable to you upon your access and use of the Site, and informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, protection, and disclosure of information we receive from users of the Site as well as your access to, and how to update and correct your personal information. UndergorundHipHop.com, LLC and its subsidiaries and affiliated companies (“us,” “we,” or “our”) operates the websites [www.undergroundhiphop.com](http://www.undergroundhiphop.com/) and [www.skratchcoin.com](http://www.skratchcoin.com/), mobile applications, and other online services offered by us that link to or reference this policy (collectively, the “Site(s)”).

Please read the Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing and/or using the Site, you accept and agree to be bound and abide by this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the Privacy Policy, please do not access or use the Site.  We may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time, and if we make material changes to it, we will notify you as appropriate.  Continuing to use the Site after we publish or communicate a notice about any changes to this Privacy Policy constitutes binding acceptance of those changes. By accessing and/or using the Site, You accept and agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy and our “ _Terms of Use_ ,” found at <http://www.undergroundhiphop.com/terms-of-use>, which are hereby incorporated by reference.

## How We Collect Personal Information

We employ commercially reasonable measures to protect your privacy while visiting our Site, endeavoring to provide a useful and productive experience.  This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect between you and the Site(s).

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Site.  While you can use many features of the Site(s) anonymously, you may be required to provide Personal Information to gain access to some of our content or services.  Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, mailing address, and phone number.  For example, we may ask you to provide us with Personal Information that can be used to contact or identify you, including information that you provide by filling in forms on our Site. This includes information provided to use or receive information about services and offerings from UndergroundHipHop.com, LLC or Skratch, Inc. For example, when you fill out the “Register Now” form or “Contact” form,” you consent to release any Personal Information provided and/or data to us.  Likewise, by submitting your Personal Information through the Site, you are consenting to receive e-mail or other applicable information from us.

## Collection and Use of Anonymous Information

We may also collect automatic, anonymous information such as browser type and version, browser language, your operating system and platform, and the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet. This information does not identify you, but is statistical data used for analytical purposes and helps us provide more relevant services to users. For example, we may use this information to administer and troubleshoot issues directly related to the Site, such as Site administration or to analyze certain trends in Site usage.

  * ## Log Information

We collect log information about your use of the online services, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the page you visited before navigating to our online services.

  * ## Device Information

We collect information about the computer or mobile device you use to access our online services, including the hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers and mobile network information.

  * ## Location Information

We may collect information about the location of your device each time you access or use one of our mobile applications or otherwise consent to the collection of this information.

  * ## Cookies

The technology we use to obtain this information includes the use of cookies.  Cookies are small files placed on the hard drive of your computer to identify you when you visit a website. You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this Site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.  Unless you have adjusted your browser setting to refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Site.  We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction, in order to better understand our customers and their needs.

  * ## Tracking

Pixels We may also collect anonymous information through the use of tracking pixels. A tracking pixel is a transparent graphic image (usually 1 pixel x 1 pixel) that is placed on a webpage and, in combination with a cookie, allows for the collection of information regarding the use of the webpage that contains the tracking pixel. We use tracking pixels to tell when you have clicked on certain website features or otherwise interacted with those features, and use that information to learn about visitor use. In some cases, we use third-party service providers to help us collect and analyze this anonymous information.

  * ## Google Analytics

We have enabled Google Analytics, to collect data about our traffic through the use of Google  advertisements and other anonymous identifiers. We use Google Analytics cookies and other cookies to compile data to better understand users and provide users with a more tailored experience.  You can opt out of Google Analytics by visiting Google’s Opt-Out Browser Add-on website [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

## How We Protect Information

We have taken commercially reasonable precautions to protect the data and information under our control from misuse, loss, or alteration.  Our security measures include industry standard technology and equipment to help protect your data.  Unfortunately, considering the open nature of the internet, no system can ensure complete security and you should take steps to protect your information and transmissions to the Site.

We retain the Personal Information you provide while your account is in existence or as needed to provide you services. We may retain your Personal Information if retention is reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations, meet applicable regulatory requirements, or enforce this Privacy Policy. We may retain Personal Information, for a limited period of time, if requested by law enforcement.

## How We Use your Information

We may use and/or disclose Information that we collect or you provide as described in this Privacy Policy:

  * To present our Site and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information or services that you request from us, such as sending you certain information about UndergroundHipHop.com, LLC and Skratch, Inc services and offerings.
  * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * Between and among our current and future parents, affiliates, subsidiaries and other companies under common control and ownership.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of UndergroundHipHop.com, LLC and Skratch, Inc assets, where information held by UndergroundHipHop.com, LLC and Skratch, Inc about our Site users is among the assets transferred.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * With your express consent or at your direction.

## Opting Out

If at any time after registering for information, you change your mind about receiving information from us, send us a request specifying your new choice. Simply send your request to [service@undergroundhiphop.com](mailto:service@undergroundhiphop.com).

## Links to Third Party Sites

Our Site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the privacy policy of every website you visit. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party sites or services.

## Children Under the Age of 13

We do not sell products or services for purchase by anyone under the age of 13. In accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we will never knowingly request or solicit personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13, without verifiable parental consent. In the event that we receive actual knowledge that we have collected such personal information without the requisite and verifiable parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as is practical.

## Compliance with Legal Process

Please be aware that we will release specific Personal Information about you if required to do so in order to comply with applicable law or any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order. We may also choose to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

## Users in California

We do not share your Personal Information with third parties for direct marketing.  California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of the Site who are California residents to request and obtain from us a list of what personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year and the names and addresses of those third parties. Requests may be made only once a year and are free of charge. Under Section 1798.83, we currently do not share any Personal Information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

## Policy Updates

We may choose to change this Privacy Policy at any time in our sole discretion. Any updates to our Privacy Policy will be posted on this page, so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Continued use of the Site following our posting of the change notice will constitute binding acceptance of those changes.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [service@undergroundhiphop.com](mailto:service@undergroundhiphop.com) .
